[Music]
it starts with a simple but powerful
mission for clean sport stand with
athletes to Champion their right to
clean sport Inspire true and healthy
Sport and promote the Integrity of sport
Guided by this Mission we stand with
athletes and for athletes from the start
of their careers to the day they retire
when they first Enter Sport we are there
to help them learn the lessons and
values for Success on and off off the
field as they ascend to higher levels of
sport we are there with education and
resources that help them navigate the
antidoping process when their success
makes them eligible for testing we are
there with a friendly face and
consistent protocols to guide them
through the process when they have a
question about substances and methods we
have experts available a phone call away
and at the Forefront of the effort to
solve the most complex anti-doping
questions if they run into issues with
the rules we are there with a fair
adjudication process that protects the
rights of all
athletes and when the day comes for them
to start a new Journey we are there to
process their retirement and celebrate
their commitment to clean sport from the
first whistle to the final buzzer usada
is standing with athletes to Champion
their right to clean sport inspiring
true and healthy Sport and promoting the
Integrity of sport